export const data = {
    "data": [
      {
        "quesId": 1,
        "question": "What is the main purpose of Piggyvest?",
        "options": ["Investing in stocks", "Saving money", "Online shopping", "Cryptocurrency trading"],
        "answer": 1
      },
      {
        "quesId": 2,
        "question": "Which of the following is NOT a feature of Piggyvest?",
        "options": ["Savings", "Investments", "Loans", "Social media networking"],
        "answer": 3
      },
      {
        "quesId": 3,
        "question": "What is the minimum amount required to start saving on Piggyvest?",
        "options": ["₦100", "₦1,000", "₦5,000", "₦10,000"],
        "answer": 0
      },
      {
        "quesId": 4,
        "question": "Which investment option is NOT offered by Piggyvest?",
        "options": ["Mutual funds", "Real estate", "Treasury bills", "Cryptocurrencies"],
        "answer": 1
      },
      {
        "quesId": 5,
        "question": "What is the purpose of Piggyvest's 'Flex Dollar' feature?",
        "options": ["Investing in foreign stocks", "Saving in foreign currency", "Making international transfers", "Purchasing digital assets"],
        "answer": 1
      },
      {
        "quesId": 6,
        "question": "Which financial institution partners with Piggyvest to provide loans?",
        "options": ["Guaranty Trust Bank", "Access Bank", "Zenith Bank", "First Bank of Nigeria"],
        "answer": 0
      },
      {
        "quesId": 7,
        "question": "What does Piggyvest's 'PiggyFlex' feature allow users to do?",
        "options": ["Access instant loans", "Invest in agriculture", "Donate to charities", "Earn interest on savings"],
        "answer": 3
      },
      {
        "quesId": 8,
        "question": "Which of the following is a Piggyvest savings challenge?",
        "options": ["Piggybank", "Thrift collector", "Target savings", "Safelock"],
        "answer": 2
      },
      {
        "quesId": 9,
        "question": "What is the purpose of Piggyvest's 'SafeLock' feature?",
        "options": ["Investing in high-risk assets", "Securing savings for a fixed period", "Protecting against fraud", "Enabling peer-to-peer transfers"],
        "answer": 1
      },
      {
        "quesId": 10,
        "question": "Which of the following is a Piggyvest referral program reward?",
        "options": ["Cashback on purchases", "Discounts on loans", "Additional interest on savings", "Free insurance coverage"],
        "answer": 2
      }
    ]
  }